Hello friends, welcome to
your own YouTube channel Indian Market.
In this video, we will talk about some companies in which you
may see an upside or downside
because these companies are going to present their return
numbers today. So if you are
thinking of investing in these companies,
the update is definitely going to be important for you.
So let's
start the video. First of all, if we
talk about the company, Bank of India is quite
good, or the fundamentals are also quite
good. But you
can see here, if we talk about its maximum chat
button, then
if we calculate from the top level, you
can see here that
we see a decline of around 85% here. So
friends, if we look at the investment most, then
I don't like this company from anywhere.
If you want to
invest in a PSU bank, then friends,
you will not find a better bank than SBI, otherwise
you can also ignore it completely.
Apart from this, if we talk about the next
company, its name is Delta.  If we
talk about the maximum chat button, then you
can see here that more ups and downs are
visible, so I am
not seeing much growth here.
If its performance is seen from 2007 till now, then
you can see here a
return of about 450 percent,
so the company is good, but
I am not seeing much growth here,
due to which I also
completely award this stock. If you want,
friends, you can also consider it because
this video is only for educational purposes. If we
talk about the market cap of the company, then
see, you can see the boy of 5.76 train, then it is
looking quite attractive,
but friends, you are
seeing almost no growth here.
Apart from this, if we talk about the next company, then you
can see here that ICICI
Lombara, if we talk about its maximum
chat button, then you can see here
that if we talk from 2017 till now, then
see, if we talk about 5 years and 6 years, then
approximately  If we look at 83% here, then
friends, I do
n't see much growth here. You
can see here that if we
calculate from the level above this, then this
stock still sees a decline of around 22%.
Okay, friends, a decline is
not a sin. If the company's
performance is good, then
you can definitely see momentum in the stock as well.
But
friends, I did not see much growth in this company. So, if
seen from a long-term perspective, I do
not like this company at all. The company has very good
fundamentals and is quite strong. And the group that is
associated with it definitely belongs
to a big group. But
friends, due to not seeing any growth here,
I completely award this stock.
Apart from this, if we talk about the
next company, then look at the company associated with the same group,
ICICI
Prudential Life. If you
look at its maximum chat button, then from 2016 onwards,
we saw its listing above NSC,
but till now, if  If we talk about it, then we are
seeing returns of only 53% here, so friends, we will
not see any growth here,
due to which I am not completely against this stock.
If we talk about the next company, then
here we can see the name of Metro Brand Company.
If we
talk about its maximum chat pattern, then
we can see returns of 80% here,
but look at its listing, friends, it is
not very old, we saw the listing of this company within about 150 years,
so from now till now,
we are seeing positive returns of about 80%
and you all must be aware that
we also got to see a lot of pressure in the market,
but look at this stock,
you can see here that
we did not see much pressure or any big bike people, so whoever
has this company, I feel that
you should hold it for the long term.
If we talk about its market cap,
then its market cap is around Rs 23 crore, yes,
it is
seen to be a little expensive,
but friends, the quality in the company is good.
And whenever there was a fall in it, there would
definitely be investors from the lower level, they would be
ready to bank, due to which
you will definitely see it around the level.
Apart from this, if we talk about the next
company, then look at Tata Metaliks, if we talk about the
financials of this company, then
you guys see here I do not like the financials of the company at all. If
you look here
after December 2021, then very poor
performance was seen. Apart from this,
if we talk about March 2022, then
poor performance was seen there too.
Apart from this, if we talk about June, then look here
also we got to see very poor performance of the company.
And if we talk about the September
order, then look here also
we got to see poor numbers of the company. So
friends, if we look continuously, then
I am seeing poor performance of this company.
If we talk about reading the maximum chat of this company, then
you guys got to
see positive returns of about 8217% here,
but you can see here that for many
years we were seeing this stock stuck in an iron,
but look here
But we are also seeing a lot of ups and downs,
so in which you
can definitely hold this company,
see friends, the company is not a bad company
and everyone knows that it is a company associated with the Tata Group, so the
chances of your money getting lost here are very less,
and talking about the market cap also, it is
seen to be around 2.63 crores, so
whoever has this should invest, but
friends,
I will not advise you at all to invest in this company,
and anyway, friends, this video is only for
educational purposes, so here I do
not give any buy or sell recommendation,
and if we talk about the fundamentals of the company, then
I did not find it that special, so
friends, this video was only for
educational purposes, here I do
not give any buy or sell recommendation, and
I have not even registered everyone, thank you very
much